Excuse me, sir. Question for you. How
did you become wealthy? [laughter]
>> And how would you know that I am?
>> I could tell, man. You got that look,
man.
>> Well, let me tell you. It's an original
story. I'm a Holocaust survivor.
>> How old are you?
>> I am now over 90.
>> I'm going on 85.
>> 79.
>> 68.
>> You want to tell them how you got rich?
>> I did. I started. My dad was a drunk,
beat my mom. She was 39 when she died in
front of me. I was 16. Became the
largest mowing company of individually
mowing military bases all over the
country. just sold the company 5 years
ago.
>> How much did you sell?
>> It was 10 million.
>> It was about a billion millions.
>> More than 10 million.
>> Yeah. Oh, yeah. Yeah.
>> More than 50 million.
>> Yes.
>> No, you didn't.
>> I was one of the largest in the world.
>> Were you actually tell the secret of
getting rich?
>> You're 90 years old today. If you could
leave one last message with the world.
What would that be?
>> Oh my god.
>> I'm about to walk up to 90year-old
billionaires and ask them how they
became wealth. I'm talking about people
worth hundreds of millions, even
billions of dollars and have spent
decades building empires. But here's the
craziest thing. These people almost
never [music] talk to camera. So guys, I
just did something insane. I just flew
out to Scottsdale, Arizona, one of the
richest, most private cities in America
to go and find these [music]
billionaires and ask them one question.
How did you get rich? But here's the
twist. The first millionaire I interview
in this video is already in his 60s. And
with every interview, they only get
older. And what they're about to say
could change the way you think about
money forever. This video is brought to
you by Shopify. With that being said,
let's get this video on the way.
[music]
>> Uh, real quick, question for you, sir.
Is this your Rolls-Royce?
>> No, it's not.
>> Real quick. I have a channel with 22
million followers. I've interviewed 53
billionaires in the last 5 years. I ask
entrepreneurs how they made it for the
younger generation. Do you think I could
do a quick interview with the gentleman
in the back? I just interviewed Quick.
Could I could I get you real quick for
30 seconds, sir? I promise you it'll be
worth it, sir. Is that okay?
>> Which side do you want? You want
>> Let me go get over here. Let me get over
here. How you doing, sir?
>> Maybe this isn't mine.
>> How did you get rich, sir? What did you
do?
>> How did I get rich? I tell you the
secret to getting rich. You got to have
big balls.
>> Yeah.
>> Because if you're afraid, you're never
going to make the move that you need to
make. You got to work for yourself. And
you got to find something that appeals
to everybody.
>> What was your main company?
>> I had a lot of them, but I was one of
the largest online lenders in the world.
>> Were you actually How did you get into
this business? It doesn't seem like a
very sexy business. [laughter]
>> It's sexy when you made the kind of
money I made.
>> And what was the most amount of money
you made in a single year? My biggest
year, I made about $60 million for
myself.
>> How did you scale this company from,
let's say, a $1 million company to a $10
million business? Like, what's the
secret to scaling a business in today's
world?
>> Well, you have to have demand, first of
all. If you have the demand for the
business, it's scalable. And you can't
be afraid to make moves to be a big boy.
You're going to eat big. And if you
don't want to do that, then you'll
always stay a small guy. I started in
that business way after a lot of other
guys in that business, and we went past
them. Why? Cuz I wasn't afraid to take a
chance.
>> 100%.
>> Have you ever beened over in business
before?
>> Oh, sure. I mean, you got to qualify
that. silver in business. I always took
a majority ownership. So, have I had
some people who were not honest, who
tried to discriminate? Sure. But over
business, no, because I'm going to be in
charge.
>> Why do most businesses fail in today's
world? Eight out of 10 companies don't
make it past 5 years. Why do you see
most people go out of business in
today's world?
>> I'll tell you exactly why. Most of them
are under finance. If you don't have the
pockets to stay around during the tough
time, you don't make it through. You can
have the greatest idea in the world, but
if you can't get through to the point of
profitability, and most people start
with way too little money. So, that's
that. Yeah. So, you like the idea of
raising money before starting a business
or do you think bootstrapping because
the problem with taking in a lot of
investors is what sometimes happens. You
give away control and almost decision-m
so do you like taking on investors
there's a risk there?
>> No, no, no. I never I never give
control. You want to have some of your
own money and you want to go get seed
money and help you but let them be loans
not owning your company.
>> So, you weren't afraid to borrow money
from banks.
>> I didn't borrow money from I borrow
money from guys who who believed in me.
>> How did you have the conviction to
borrow money from successful people?
>> Oh, it was easy. We were friends. They
trusted me and uh they made a lot of
money right along with me. So, it was
good. I mean, I got to run.
>> Two last ones real quick. What's one
lesson about money that banks don't want
people to know? [laughter]
>> I'll tell you what it is. Here's here's
what banks do. They give you a umbrella
when the sun is shining and it starts
raining, they take the umbrella away.
When you really need money, you're not
getting it from a bank. They don't want
to take any risk. So, they're going to
give you money when they know they're
getting paid and they don't give a when
you need money, you go forget about it.
>> How old are you today?
>> Ah, I'm way too young to tell you that.
>> How old are you? How old are you?
>> I'm in my 60s.
>> My last question. If me and you died
tomorrow and you had one more message to
leave with the younger generation, what
would that be?
>> Treat everybody like you treat yourself.
Be fair. Be honest. Don't screw anybody
and do the right thing. You got to work
your ass off. It doesn't come easy.
>> Do you believe in God?
>> 100% I do. You want to hear a great
story?
>> Yes, sir. Please.
>> My first career as a minister. I
pastored a church until I was 30 years
old. So, yeah. Great. Great. [laughter]
Last question.
>> Thank you so much for your time and I
appreciate you, sir. Could I just show
you real quick before we I just want to
show you the channel that way you know
what it is. We interview billionaires
all over the world. It's called the
school of hard knocks. So, here's us
right here. Me and Tom industry did you
decide to pursue a career right there.
Thank you for stopping. It means a lot
guys. Look, that guy was not rich. He
was wealthy and he was given a million
dollars worth of game. I mean, that's
the type of stuff in business that's not
taught in university. And I love the
fact that he talks about the reason my
business fails is very simple. They're
under capitalized. And I remember a
billionaire in Palm Beach telling me one
time, "For every dollar you think you
need to get into business, add 10."
Great interview. Business master class.
Let's keep this one rolling and go get
this next interview. You guys, come on.
Excuse me, sir. How did you get rich?
>> Huh?
>> How did you get rich?
>> That's fine.
>> Real quick, sir. I grew to another 22
million followers. I've interviewed 52
billionaires in the last 5 years like
Mark Cuban, Michael Rubin. Could I get
30 seconds with you for just for the
channel? It's to help the younger
generation. Is that okay? What what kind
of business were you in? Please. It'll
be worth it. I promise.
>> We do wholesale.
>> Wholesale? What? Real estate.
>> No, furniture, fabric, and lighting.
>> How did you get into this business?
>> I've always been interested in design.
>> Are you an entrepreneur?
>> Huh? I am.
>> What was your turning point to becoming
an entrepreneur? Like, did you work jobs
growing up or how did
>> Just knowing that other people didn't
run businesses the way I saw it that
they should be run,
>> actually.
>> Yeah.
>> And what did you take away from your
mentors? Maybe did you have any great
mentors when you started out in the
business world?
>> Well, I think everybody does when they
start.
>> What's the best piece of advice that
you've received throughout your career?
>> If it's to be, it's up to me.
>> Break that down. Yeah. Meaning, nobody's
going to come save you.
>> No one. And that's the best piece of
advice I ever had.
>> And how big is your company today? Like
what was the most amount of money you've
made in a single year?
>> Millions.
>> I hear eight figures or more than 10
million.
>> Yeah. Oh, yeah. Yeah.
>> Was it 20 million?
>> Yes.
>> More than 50 million.
>> No, you didn't. You said more than $50
million. Did you have people that
doubted you in the business world?
>> Oh, always.
>> You did.
>> Yeah. You put your blinders on.
>> Why is that?
>> Because people will always doubt you.
They always say that you don't you not
good enough to do it or not.
>> Your products that you have, do you sell
them on Shopify?
>> You just work with the interior design.
>> Are you familiar with Shopify?
>> Yes, I am.
>> You are?
>> Yeah. So, I tell everybody Shopify is
one of the greatest gifts to
entrepreneurs in today's world because
with their AI tool, it's called
Sidekick. It will literally help you
build a store in minutes and you can
start selling on there. And they also
amplified on all the different social
media platforms. Shopify is doing a ton
for entrepreneurs. Incredible. How are
you today?
>> Oh, I'm 65.
>> You look amazing for 65. So, money stays
in shape.
>> Money stays in shape.
>> So, there's a correlation between
physical health and financial successful
people, the eight, nine, and 10 figure
entrepreneurs. What do you notice among
the most successful business owners and
entrepreneurs that you've seen?
>> I think most billionaires I meet are
extremely nice people.
>> They're humble.
>> They're humble. People think that
wealthy people are these terrible
people.
>> They don't have to be. Yeah.
>> Often times the brokeest people I've met
are the most bitter people in the world.
Exactly. It's a crazy thing, isn't it?
Were you a good salesman?
>> Absolutely.
>> You were What was your secret to sales?
Something that you always went back to.
>> You know what? We didn't really work on
the like tactic stuff. Like we're not
hardcore sales people. We have good
product and it just works that way.
>> You know, people don't want your
business. Okay, go somewhere else and
come back when you realize that we're
>> when you realize we're good. Yeah. I
mean, we represent an incredible
manufacturer. So,
>> what did you learn about pricing?
>> Pricing is what it is. It doesn't really
matter to people. As long as it's good
quality. People want quality, they
they're going to buy from us.
>> So, it's true when they say that price
is only an issue when value is absent.
>> Yes.
>> Well, you have amazing advice, sir.
>> I appreciate that, man. Thank you so
much for your time, man. Have a great
day, sir.
>> Guys, we just interviewed an
entrepreneur who's doing over $50
million a year. 50 M. Did you hear what
the best piece of advice he ever got
was? He said, "If it's to be, it's up to
me." And that's exactly what
entrepreneurship is. Look, nobody's
coming to build that business for you.
You have to take the first step. And
that's why I was telling him, look, I
genuinely believe Shopify is one of the
greatest gifts for entrepreneurs in
today's world because Shopify is where
you can turn your idea into a real
business. You can create your store,
list your products, take payments, and
do all of that. Do everything in just
one place. And what's crazy is how easy
they made it. Now, with Shopify's AI
store builder and Sidekick, it's
literally like having an AI co-founder
working with you because you can
literally describe your idea, build your
store, write product descriptions, and
start selling in minutes. You don't need
to know how to code. You don't need this
massive team. Shopify removes the
friction that prevents most people from
ever starting a business. So, if you've
been waiting for that perfect sign,
waste no more time, guys. Start your
Shopify store today by going down to the
link in the description of this video
and turn your idea into a real business
today. Now, with that being said, let's
go get this next interview.
>> Excuse me, sir.
>> Question for you. How did you get rich?
[laughter]
>> I have a channel with 22 million
followers. I interview millionaires and
billionaires to help the younger
generation in business. What did you do
for a living?
>> I was a contractor.
>> Did you own your own kind of firm or own
company? Did you come from a lot of
money growing up? No,
>> you didn't.
>> Had nothing.
>> So, what was your turning point to
financial freedom? Was there a moment
early on where you were like, I'm gonna
go out there and create a little empire
from
>> education to start with?
>> So, college degree you thought was
necessary for you.
>> What was your first step after college?
Did you go get a job first or did you go
right to doing your own thing?
>> No, I got a job first.
>> And when did you know you wanted to
become an entrepreneur?
>> Right away.
>> What was the most amount of money you
made in a single year?
>> It was about a billion, but I can't tell
you how much we made.
>> Did you say a billion dollars?
>> A billion.
>> What was your company? What was the name
of it?
>> Kitchell. How old are you today?
>> 79.
>> How do you stay so sharp at 79?
>> Keep moving.
>> You keep moving.
>> Just keep moving.
>> You have people that doubted you in the
business world.
>> Always. Of course.
>> I got to run.
>> Last one. If me last one, if 79 today,
if if me and you died tomorrow, right?
>> Yes, sir.
>> Yeah. Yeah. If if me and you died
tomorrow and you had one more message to
leave with the younger generation, what
would that be?
>> Oh, I don't know.
>> Give me one more message. One more life
lesson. This is to help people.
>> How are you?
>> Good. How are you?
>> You're the guy.
>> Yes, sir. How are you?
>> Johnny Hoy from Omaha.
>> James Duma. Nice to meet you, sir. And
you and your brother do it, right?
>> Absolutely.
>> That is so cool.
>> How are you doing?
>> Great.
>> You want to tell them how you got rich?
>> I did. I started My dad was a drunk,
beat my mom. She was 39 when she died in
front of me. I was 16. Raised four
sisters and a brother and started with a
lawnmower. Became the largest mowing
company of individually mowing military
bases all over the country. Just sold
the company 5 years ago. Now I got 2600
apartments stocks and from Omaha,
Nebraska, Shire Hathaway.
>> How much did you sell the company for?
Well, lawnmowing companies don't sell
like the billionaires do.
>> But how much did you sell?
>> It was 10 million.
>> $10 million, sir. Congratulations.
>> Never gave up. Gave God the glory.
>> You faced a ton of adversity. Talk to
somebody at rock bottom. What's an
actionable step that people can take to
get their life back on track?
>> Never give up. Give God the glory. Never
say I can't. Always say I can. And take
care of your customer. And your customer
will take care of you.
>> Who is your God?
>> Lord Jesus Christ, my Lord and Savior.
>> How did you know Jesus is real, man? I'm
a firm believer in Jesus Christ as well.
is the miracles of me not being what my
dad was. And then 5 years ago, I found
out through 23 and me wasn't even my
dad. Thought I was half Croatian from
Yugoslavia. Found out I'm a half Italian
from Serno, Italy.
>> Now, you built and sold a lawnmowing
company. Okay. I want to ask you, it's
not necessarily a super sexy business.
So, is it true that people can get rich
with a lot of different companies in
today's
>> but stay in what you know? Warren
Buffett, I've had dinner with him 12
times at charity deals and he always
says stay what you know. Don't get in
another man's game.
>> So, in other words, focus and not
diversify. Exactly.
>> But when you sold your company, where'd
you put that money?
>> Stocks and real estate. All since I was
16, I've been doing stocks and real
estate. The biggest thing is net worth
means nothing and cash flow means
everything.
>> That is what I learned from the
recession of 2008 to 2012. Everything
was net worth. Net worth. Net worth
until you have a lot of net worth and no
cash flow. Cash flow is everything.
>> That's game right there. I love that.
>> And the biggest thing is is I've never
seen a hearse pull a U-Haul yet. So, no
one's takes it with them. Help others
while you're here. Make an impact. I've
given away over 10 million to charity,
loving people.
>> How old are you today?
>> 68.
>> 68 years old.
>> I was 16 when I started the lawn
business.
>> You spent a lot of time around
billionaires. You had lunch with Warren
Buffett 12 times. When you think about
all the billionaires and the most
successful people, you know, what's that
one thing they all have in common?
>> Humbleness.
>> They're humble
>> and simplify your life, the humbleness,
and listen to others. When I meet
somebody, I don't say, "How'd you get
rich? What'd you do wrong?" So I can
learn. Money buys experience. Experience
winds up with the money.
>> Oh my goodness. You You're fooled. These
sound bites. They don't teach this stuff
in school. You know that, right?
>> Life is common sense. Do onto others you
want them to do unto you.
>> I love that. You have amazing advice,
sir.
>> All right.
>> Thank you for your time. I appreciate
that, man. Have you seen the channel
before?
>> All the time. Will you send me your
card?
>> Absolutely.
>> I'll send you my book and some Omaha
steak.
>> Thank you, my friend. Have a good one,
sir. Thank you. Wow.
>> So, look, I just finished up
interviewing a contractor that I guess
made a billion dollars in a year, and he
was in the rush to get out of there.
That guy right there gave us the time a
day and just gave us a phenomenal
interview. grew up in an abusive
household. Saw his mother getting beat
and he built an absolute empire and of
all businesses. Lawnmowing, guys.
Lawnming, man. He put his head down and
he built an incredible company that he
sold for eight figures. Incredible
advice right there from that gentleman.
I'm going to forever remember that
interview right there. Let's go get this
next one. Wow. Arch, guys. So, I have a
very special surprise for you all right
here. So, look, we're out here in
Scottsdale. As you know, this is one of
the millionaire billionaire capitals of
the United States. I went into a coffee
shop to get a little coffee cuz we've
been out here for hours filming. And I
had a gentleman come up to me and said,
"Yo, I'm a huge fan of your channel. My
grandfather, who I think I looked him up
and is 84 years old, became a
billionaire, I believe, through owning
amusement parks." Amusement parks, guys.
I don't know about you guys, but I've
never met anybody that owns amusement
parks. And I thought I've interviewed
people from every single industry on
this channel. But I guess I haven't. So,
we're about to go figure out how the
amusement park billionaire made his
money, how he got the money to buy these
amusement parks, and the secret to
becoming wealthy and building
generational wealth. So, let's go meet
up with him right now and go see what he
has to say. All right, guys. Look, we
just got to our destination out here in
Scottsdale where we're going to be
interviewing the 84year-old mogul, the
amusement park mogul. You guys, we're
going up to the door right now to meet
him and figure out how he got rich and
exactly how you can follow in his
footsteps and his blueprint. Come on.
>> Oh my goodness.
>> How you doing, sir? [clears throat]
>> How are you?
>> Good. It's great to meet you, my friend.
>> I'm George.
>> I'm James. That's James. Certainly, my
pleasure.
>> Yeah. We were letting our our audience
know. We were letting them know that
I've interviewed about a thousand
millionaires and billionaires in the
last 5 years. And and and and [laughter]
>> you're in the wrong place.
>> No, no, no, no. And and so I've
[clears throat] interviewed people that
were in the tech industry that were in
real estate that were in all these
different businesses. You were in the
amusement park business.
>> Well, that's one of my fortees is
amusement parks. I kind of got started
when I was young, actually, at the young
age of 15.
>> Wow.
>> I'm better at show and tell than I am
probably talking.
>> Sure.
>> I'd like to maybe take you guys on a
quick little tour for five or six
minutes.
>> Would love that. So, uh,
>> this is a beautiful pad [clears throat]
you got out here.
>> Well, thank you. I'm a doer more than a
talker.
>> Sure.
>> I tell people, they say you're a
workaholic. And I tell people that, uh,
if you're doing it for yourself, it's
not work. If you're doing it for someone
else, it is.
>> So, I said, I've had the blessing since
I was about 19 that I've never worked
for anybody else. And so, it's really
not work. Seriously.
>> How old do you know?
>> Going on 85.
>> You don't look 85 at all.
>> Well, you must be getting older. Your
eyes are
>> dimming on you a little bit.
>> Go ahead.
>> Thank you. All right, you guys. Hey, my
guy's backyard is a straight resort, you
guys. Look at Look at this place. This
place is insane right here, you guys.
Wow. Hey, I didn't know that you could
build resorts in a backyard.
>> Well, yeah. The city doesn't know about
it. So, you want to ask me what my
biggest accomplishment is in life?
>> Yes, sir.
>> I have 66 grandchildren.
>> No, you do not. Are you serious?
>> I'll show you a picture.
>> Okay. So, I have seven kids and between
me and my wife, there's 90 94 of us.
>> Oh my goodness.
>> I'm assuming you got family reunion back
here. know well here and a couple other
places but it but my advice is marry
right and have kids cuz when you get my
age like that it's best thing you can
have. So, uh, siblings.
>> I have, uh, one older brother. I'm 23
and he's 25. I guess he just turned 26.
So, wow. Look at this right here.
>> I'm kind of into little golf is kind of
my forte. So,
>> yeah, we're not at a mini golf course.
This is your backyard right here.
>> I'm going to just show you a couple more
things over here. So, I'm a real avid
hunter and I've hunted all over the
world and I ended up filling this up
with life-siz animals.
>> Oh my goodness.
>> So, the the elephant here being one of
them.
>> Yeah. This is incredible.
>> And uh, so this just gives you a little
bit of a flavor. Yes, that is amazing.
>> Bear from Peninsula of Alaska. You don't
get to see this too often.
>> This is incredible. It looks like we're
in the National History Museum right
here.
>> There you go.
>> What's your name?
>> My name is George Brimhall.
>> So, you've built how many amusement
parks?
>> So, I've built 13.
>> So, how in the world did you get money
to buy amusement parks?
>> Well, I ended up beg borrow. I was going
to say steal, but I didn't steal.
>> You come out with people like you that
are successful that believe in you. They
know your work ethic.
>> Some people that took a chance on you.
>> Absolutely. If I you ask me to give
advice to young people, marry a great
gal that likes kids. Because when you
get my age, you don't don't think about
the theme parks. You don't think about
the golf courses you've done or the
shopping centers you've built or the
homes you've built as much as you do the
kids that you have and your grandkids.
>> How long have you been married?
>> 55 years.
>> How long have you been faithful?
>> Let me just put it this way, okay? The
best relationship a person could have,
in my opinion, is with their wife. I
think that's the person you'd trust the
most, the mo the person you'd have the
most confidence in and the most desire
to please would be your wife.
Unfortunately, over 50% of marriages end
up in divorce, which is sad.
>> Are you still in love with your wife?
>> Well, I am. Unfortunately, she passed
away about three and a half years ago,
but I still love her.
>> Sorry for your loss, sir.
>> No. Well, we're all on the same road.
Some are just ahead of others, so I'll
join her.
>> What was the secret to having such a
successful marriage?
>> My religion keeps me true to my wife. Do
>> you believe in God? Well, this New York
big. No, I don't believe I'm past I'm
past the faith. I know
>> who is your God.
>> God the the eternal father and I believe
in his son Jesus Christ and I and the
spirit, the Holy Ghost. Let me tell you
a secret, okay? I believe in fasting.
When you fast, it's something that you
have to do physically. And and if you
fast for a purpose with the Lord
involved and you're praying and you're
saying, "Listen, this is I got a
decision here. I don't know who to
marry. I don't know what school to go
to. I don't know whether I should get
involved in this investment or not or I
I'm really not sure on this. You know,
if you fast at the end of 24 hours when
you go forward thereafter, he's your
partner.
>> I love that.
>> He's your partner.
>> You said you have 66 grandchildren.
>> 66.
>> Let me ask you this right here. What is
one lesson about life that you are going
to instill in your big family before you
leave this earth?
>> You get out of life what you put in it.
You can be a slacker or you can be a
chief. If you want to succeed in life,
you have to set a goal and you have to
work for it. And when that's done, then
you need to set another goal and work
for it. So, we're we're put down here to
develop our talents and improve upon our
situation that we have and make it
better for other people.
>> What is the deepest life quote that
you've ever heard?
>> I tell young kids all the time, "Would
you like to be wealthy?" And they say,
"Yeah, absolutely. Would you, you know,
like to look like you guys? Biceps,
muscles, chest, everything?" Absolutely.
Would you like to be smart?
>> Absolutely. Well, you've all heard this
one. Early to bed, early to rise makes a
man healthy, wealthy, and wise.
>> I love that right there. Well, sir, you
have amazing advice.
>> Well, I don't know about that, but it's
been a real pleasure. You guys are
energetic, young, and ambitious,
[snorts] and you're going to
>> you'll you'll dwarf what I do.
>> Thank you so much for your time. I
really appreciate that, sir.
>> Well, guys, we just interviewed an 84y
old billionaire that owns 13 amusement
parks. And look, this video has been
insane. We've interviewed millionaires
and billionaires in their 60s, in their
70s, in their 80s. But look, we're back
on the streets now to see if we can take
things up a notch and go find the oldest
living millionaires and billionaires
that live out here. Let's go see who we
can find.
>> Excuse me, sir. question for you. How
did you become wealthy? [laughter]
>> And how would you know that I am?
>> I could tell, man. You got that look,
man. What did you do? What was your
career? What was your business?
>> Well, let me tell you, it's an original
story. I'm a Holocaust survivor. And as
a Holocaust survivor in Europe, you come
back to the United States. You've gone
through so much that you have absolutely
no fear of anything else happening to
you. You take each day as a new day and
you fight for it. I got my own aerospace
industry distributorship. I have 32
people working for me.
>> How old are you?
>> I am now over 90. Just celebrated my
90th birthday.
>> Are you serious?
>> You you were in concentration camps
though.
>> We were a family of eight. I got two
brothers, two sisters that died in
Oshvitz. I escaped with my mother and my
sister and then she married a GI. She
was a war bride and that's how she got
to the United States and then we
followed. What did going through the
Holocaust teach you about overcoming
adversity? Cuz I mean there were a lot
of people that didn't survive.
>> It's exactly you're using the correct
word survival in any way that you can. I
mean a meal for me in hiding for
example. The best thing that happened to
me is see a cockroach because that's
protein, a rat, a mouse, anything to eat
in the woods.
>> How old were you during the Holocaust?
>> Five. But you learn fast. You grow up
fast.
>> Five up until about what age?
>> Well, the war uh ended in 45. So around
12. And I came to the United States at
16. I haven't had a single day of school
education. Not a single day. Everything
I learn, I learn in life. And now
>> you didn't go to school when you came to
America.
>> When I was 16, I came here. I had no
money. I couldn't go to any school. I
had to support myself.
>> So when you came to America, when you
were starting out, you were essentially
kind of at rock bottom. You didn't have
a lot of your family. Let's talk to
somebody right now. They're at rock
bottom. They don't know the first thing
to do. What's that first actionable step
somebody watching can take to really get
turn their life around just like you
did?
>> To my girls, one of them is going
through right now. She's a flabotamist.
So I said, "Why are you doing the job
and getting 40% of the money? Why don't
you start the job as a phabotamist and
make a reputation for yourself?
>> You should become an entrepreneur."
>> Exactly. And that's exactly what she's
in the process of doing.
>> Do you believe in God today?
>> When you're asking me about God, got the
wrong guy here. I said to myself, there
is no God that could possibly do that. I
mean, innocent brothers and sisters,
they were 13, 14, and 50 when they died.
>> You ever try to pray to God today?
>> No.
>> And when they say you find religion in
the trenches, well, I was in Korea
during the war. I didn't find it in the
trenches. I saw my guys die left and
right. I didn't say, "Oh, God saved me
now. I need you." It didn't come to me.
It I saw too many hard things in my life
to believe that if there is a God,
>> kind of allow that to happen. Yeah,
>> but I'm still a happy guy. Would you
believe that at 90 I'm dating?
>> You're dating at 90 years old?
>> Well, you don't look You look 70, man. I
know you don't believe in God. I do
believe in God, though. I am a Christian
and I would like to pray for you at some
point. You know why I believe? Cuz look
at how handsome you are. You You a
creation like you has to have a
designer, man. You know what? That's
just my personal opinion.
>> Well, listen. I will never argue believe
in God or anything else that you want to
believe in. I think it's great for you.
That's what you need.
>> Last question for you. You're 90 years
old today. If you could leave one last
message with the world, what would that
be?
>> Oh my god. Enjoy your family. They're
gone so soon sometimes. Love each other.
Live your life with a goal in mind
without fear. In fact, I will tell you
that it's the no fear that has led me to
success. Don't be afraid to get into
something, to try something. It's not
going to happen if you don't. This was a
phenomenal conversation, man. Thank you
for your time. I appreciate you stopping
to talk to me.
>> Anytime.
>> I really appreciate it,
>> guys. That's a wrap on today's video. We
just interviewed millionaires and
billionaires in their 60s, '7s, '8s, and
'9s. I need y'all to stop right now,
like and subscribe for amazing content
we got coming every week to the school
of hard knocks. And look, I want to go a
step further. I want to give you direct
access to my billionaire network. Every
single week, I host live calls with the
eight, nine, and 10 figureure
entrepreneurs that you see me interview
on the school of hard knock. If you want
access to my billionaire network right
now, go down, click the link in the
description of this video to join the
school of mentors today and I'll see you
on the inside. With that being said, see
you in the next